gamnesia.com 2009-08-20

# Gamnesia - Video Game Plot Summaries, HD Video Playthroughs, Game Music, Game Ending Videos, Character Analysis, Game Scripts and More

Welcome to www.Gamnesia.com (the "Site"), gaming's first web portal dedicated to reminding gamers of their gaming experiences. We understand that your privacy online is important to you, especially when conducting your business. This Privacy Policy will inform you of our policies in handling personal information about our Visitors and Members. Our Visitors use the site but have not registered with us as registered users. Our Members are registered users of the Site.

"Personally Identifiable Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (i.e., without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

· What personally identifiable information is collected? We collect information from its users who apply to become Members: the name, address, age and email of the Member. This information is collected in order for us to evaluate the eligibility of the user for Membership and use of the Site.

· What organization is collecting the information? We collect and securely store the information submitted by Members in their Registration. Our third party service vendors who may provide such services as credit may collect other information from our Members of the Site. We do not control how these third parties use such information.

· How the information is used? We use personal information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings to you, and to fulfill your buying requests on the Site. We will email you about the Site, about research, purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or related to the subject matter of the Site. We also use personal information to contact you in response to specific inquiries you have made to us, or to provide you with specific information and services you have requested or agreed to be notified about.

· With whom may the information be shared? We may share aggregated information about our Members, including also the demographics of our Members with our directors, agencies and third party vendors. We may only share personal information about you with third parties if you have permitted us to do so. We also offer you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

· Are Cookies Used on the Site? Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Members

· Is Submission of Personal Information Optional? Visitors are not required to submit personal information to use the Site. However, there are portions of the Site limited to Members only. Only Members may enter into transactions on the Site and use certain Site services. Submission of personal information is required to become a Member.

· Disclosure of personal information to comply with law. We will disclose personal information in order to comply with a Court Order or subpoena, or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose personal information where reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Members.

· How does the Site keep personal information secure? Our employees are made aware of our security policy and practices. The personal information of our Visitors and Members is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to that information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, which is collected, used, or disseminated, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet.

· How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in the information? Members may contact us to update personal information about them or correct any inaccuracies by contacting us using this form.

· Can a Member delete or deactivate information collected by the Site? We provide Members with a mechanism to delete/deactivate personal information from the site's database upon request by contacting contacting us using this form. However, because of backups, and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Member's entry without some residual information. A Member who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will be functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.

· What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes? We will let our Visitors and Members know about changes to our privacy practices by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing the policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of your personal information, which you have previously asked not to be disclosed, we will contact you to notify you of the change and allow you to prevent such disclosure.

· Certain Business Transactions . In the event that the Company, or substantially all the assets of the Company, are acquired by one or more outside parties as the result of a merger, sale, consolidation, or other business transfer, the personal information of our Members may be part of the acquired assets.

· OTHER:

· This Site is not directed at children. Members are required to be 13 years old and older.

· Links. This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours
